- samnadri@laposte.net
- 2 Rue Gouverneur Général Félix Eboué Rennes (35200)
- 28 years old
- Permis B
- Personal vehicle
- +33 6 95 92 96 94

## References

**Drapala Dawid**TEAM LEADER ELECTRICIAN
OFFSHORE, .
+48 791 631 705

## Languages

**French** 

**English** 

## **Assets**

Stress Management

**Teamwork** 

#### **Interests**

Trail running, Blike, Boxing

I have taken part in several major international trail running races.

#### Samir Nadri

# Rope Access Technician CQP 1

I've been a rope access technician in the offshore wind energy sector for two years. I have been able to acquire multiple skills within the BOP TEAM and the LV TEAM. I've taken training courses that allow me to inspect steel structures and carry out visual inspections, I can inspect and recertify anchors, fire extinguishers, srl, lifts and hoists. I have installed sensors and roxtek, fibre optics and earth cables. I would like to take my IRATA exam to be able to work internationally

#### **Education**

Hailo trainning

Hailo formation Saint- France

Advance Rescue Trainning

**SKYLOTEC FRANCE France** 

H0B0 + OGUK CHESTER STEP

May 2024 . FECAMP

Training courge PALFINGER PTM 600 crane

2023 ELEVACTION HARFLEUR France

Trainning course to Inspect and Recertify fire extinguishers (C02, WATER, POWDER, FIRETRACE)

2023 VGP France

Training to Inspect and recertify anchors, srl, + visual inspection of steel structures

2023 Altitude SERVICE France

Enhanced First Aid

**IFOPSE** France

Training course Seasight Davits Crane

Since 2023 Endiprev France

Professional degree in Renewable and Electrical Energy Management

2021 Université Savoie Mont Blanc France

## Work experience

Rope access Inspector

Since May 2024 Openr Turballe

Checking and recertify safety equipment (lifts, fire extinguishers, anchors, srl, hoist, crane)

Rope access offshore BOP TEAM +LV TEAM

From October 2022 to May 2024 Altitude 44 Fecamp Checking recertify safety equipment, fire extinguishers, anchors, srl Visual inspection of steel structures Installation of roxtec and fiber optic cable.

Rope access ON/OFFSHORE

From May 2021 to September 2021 GE hub St Nazaire Touching up paint on ropes and punchlist

Rope access silo cleaning

From January 2021 to May 2021 SILONET REGION GRAND OUEST Works in confined spaces and pressure washing

Cleaner Cleaning shop fronts)

From May 2014 to September 2024 2014PEI EPERNAY

## **Computer skills**

pack office